A Guide to the Oral History Interviews Concerning Howard Worth Smith, 1975-1984
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Oral History Interviews Concerning Howard Worth Smith, 1975-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
8731-d
This collection consists of twenty-seven cassette tape recordings.
Sharon Defibaugh
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the University of Virginia Library by Bruce J. Dierenfield, Department of History, Canisius College, Buffalo, New York, on March 31, 2000.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of twenty-seven cassette tape recordings, 1975-1984, of oral interviews conducted by Bruce J. Dierenfield (1951- ) for his biography of Congressman Howard Worth Smith of Virginia, powerful member of the House Committee on Rules. These interviews were used in Dierenfield's book, Keeper of the Rules Congressman Howard W. Smith of Virginia.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically.
Contents List
- Watkins M. Abbitt, Appomottax, Virginia 1980 Oct 31
  Audiocassette 0039
- Thomas G. Abernethy, Jackson, Mississippi 1984 Jan 11
  Audiocassette 0040
- Carl Albert 1983 Aug 3
  Audiocassette 0041
- Richard D. Bolling, Washington, D.C. 1983 May 31
  Audiocassette 0042
- Armistead L. Boothe, Alexandria, Virginia 1976 Feb 28
  Audiocassette 0043
- Albert V. Bryan, Sr., Alexandria, Virginia 1978 Nov 24
  Audiocassette 0044
- Leslie D. Campbell, Jr., Ashland, Virginia 1976 Mar 26
  Audiocassette 0045
- T. M. Carruthers, Charlottesville, Virginia 1982 Sep 8
  Audiocassette 0046
- The Rt. Rev. Samuel B. Chilton, Alexandria, Virginia 1978 Nov 11
  Audiocassette 0047
- Mrs. James M. Dyer, Rixeyville, Virginia 1979 Apr 26
  Audiocassette 0048
- Carl Elliott, Jasper, Alabama 1984 Jan 12
  Audiocassette 0049-50
- Francis B. Gouldman, Spotsylvania Court House, Virginia 1976 Mar 16
  Audiocassette 0051
- Charles A. Halleck, Rensselaer, Indiana 1983 Jun 15
  Audiocassette 0052
- H. Ryland Heflin, Ruby, Virginia 1976 Mar 18
  Audiocassette 0053
- A. Sydney Herlong, Jr., Florida 1983 Sep 11
  Audiocassette 0054
- Gordon, Lewis, The Plains, Virginia 1979 Apr 26
  Audiocassette 0055
- Virginia and Landon Mitchell, Fort Lauderdale, Florida 1979 Jan13
  Audiocassette 0056
- John W. Painter, Fredericksburg, Virginia 1976 Apr 1
  Audiocassette 0057
- W. R. Poage, Waco, Texas 1983 Oct 14
  Audiocassette 0058
- George C. Rawlings, Jr., Fredericksburg, Virginia 1975 Oct 27
  Audiocassette 0059
- George C. Rawlings, Jr., Fredericksburg, Virginia 1976 Mar 10
  Audiocassette 0060
- Violett Smith Tonahill, Jasper, Texas 1978 Dec 30, 2 cassette tapes
  Audiocassette 0061-62
- William M. Tuck, South Boston, Virginia 1979 Feb 10
  Audiocassette 0063
- Kenneth T. Whitescarver, Fork Union, Virginia 1976 Apr 19
  Audiocassette 0064
- John W. Williams, Charlottesville, Virginia 1976 Mar 17
  Audiocassette 0065